Jasper Drescher

Malmö, Sweden • jasperdre@gmail.com

Summary

Gameplay Programmer with a passion for games and open-source projects. Involved in the development of gameplay, tools and engines for multiple games and platforms. Experience with project management and pipelines. Contributor to open-source projects and attendee of game events.

Skills

Programming languages: C++, C#, Java, JavaScript, PHP, SQL, CMake **Software applications**: Visual Studio, Unity, Unreal Engine, Blender

Experience

Junior Gameplay Programmer Malmö, Sweden Massive Entertainment September 2019 – present

Junior Software Developer Arnhem, The Netherlands CortexArts *September 2014 – August 2019* • Develop tools using Unity Editor, Java and C#

- Develop physics-based gameplay mechanics using Unity Engine and C#
- Develop dynamic websites using PHP, SQL, HTML, CSS and JavaScript
- Participate in Dutch Game Garden Incubation workshops
- Created 3D art assets using 3DS Max, Blender and Adobe Photoshop

Waiter Vlissingen, The Netherlands DOK 14 July 2018 - September 2018

Retail Clerk Arnhem, The Netherlands Jumbo Supermarkten December 2014 – March 2015

Education

Bachelor of Science in Creative Media and Game Technologies Breda, The Netherlands Breda University of Applied Sciences *September 2016 – July 2020* GPA 3.29/4.0

Awards

Best Programming Year 2

IGAD Game Awards, Breda University of Applied Sciences June 2018

• Winner Best Programming for Drivinity.